Greetings. Hey.
(Sheldon:)I brought Amy here
(Sheldon:)to show her some of
the work I'm doing.
(Amy:)It's very impressive,
for theoretical work.
(Sheldon:)Do I detect a hint
of condescension?
(Amy:)I'm sorry, was I being too subtle?
(Amy:)I meant compared to the
real-world applications
(Amy:)of neurobiology,
theoretical physics is--
(Amy:)what's the word I'm looking for?--
hmm, cute.
(Leonard and Wolowitz oohing)
(Sheldon:)Are you suggesting the
work of a neurobiologist
(Sheldon:)like Babinski could ever
rise to the significance
(Sheldon:)of a physicist like
Clarke-Maxwell or Dirac?
(Amy:)I'm stating it outright.
(Amy:)Babinski eats Dirac for breakfast
(Amy:)and defecates Clarke-Maxwell.
(Sheldon:)You take that back.
(Amy:)Absolutely not.
(Amy:)My colleagues and I are mapping
(Amy:)the neurological
substrates that subserve
(Amy:)global information processing,
(Amy:)which is required for
all cognitive reasoning,
(Amy:)including scientific inquiry,
making my research ipso facto
(Amy:)prior in the ordo cognoscendi.
(Amy:)That means it's better
than his research,